Be Released to Flourish! TB Joshua Prayer
Viewers all over the world, whatever situation you are in, right now, it is time.
Where there is demand, there is supply.
There is enough anointing to give, to heal, and to deliver you.
Wherever you are, all over the world, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever situation you are in, be released, in the name of Jesus!
I say, that cancer, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever cage you are in: infirmity, generational curses, demons of all kinds.
In the name of Jesus Christ, be delivered! In the name of Jesus Christ!
Your are free.
You are restored.
I am not saying, "Be restored," I am saying, "you are restored."
Right now, confess your restoration.
You are free, in the name of Jesus Christ! Thank you Lord.
Hey! Come out!
Viewers all over the world, you can see the anointing of God.
People are putting a demand on the anointing.
Where there is a demand, there is a supply.
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be rescued, in the name of Jesus!
You are rescued, in Jesus Christ's name!
Viewers, I can see you being rescued.
I can see you being delivered.
I can see you being rescued.
I can see you being released.
Your business is released
Your career is released.
Your health is released. You are released to good health.
Your business is released to breakthrough.
Your finances are released to breakthrough.
Your career is released to flourish. Be flourished.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with our latest prophesies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.